

# **UI/UX Designer, Graphic Designer**

## **PROFICIENCY**

- UI/UX Design
- Motion Graphics
- Illustration
- Graphic Design
- Web and Interactive Design
- Branding and Style Guides

## **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

- Illustrator
- HTML
- Photoshop
- CSS
- After Effects
- JavaScript
- Adobe XD
- JQuery
- Figma
- PHP
- InDesign
- MySQL
- Sketch
- WordPress

## **SUMMARY**

Passionate UI/UX Designer, Motion Graphics Designer and Illustrator. Excellent at creating lively and colorful design, with extensive knowledge and experience in Adobe Creative Cloud Suite as well as prototyping tools such as Figma and Adobe XD.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

# Graphic Designer and Illustrator

**AAE Corporation** 

Wyandanch, NY 2023 - present

- Created graphics and illustrations for brand promotions, lists of expanses and infographics for contractors.
- Put together brand style guides and marketing materials.
- Created graphic instructions for brand promotions and Indiegogo campaigns.

# **Graphic Designer and Brand Strategist**

Kinetics Technology Corp.

Taipei, Taiwan 2021 - 2022

- Helped design company logo and style guides.
- Provided guidance and support to the team throughout the development process, ensuring that the brand's visual elements were consistent and effective across all media.

## **Executive of Art and Design**

National Taiwan Normal University - Department of Physics

Taipei, Taiwan 2012 - 2014

- Designed department uniforms.
- Designed posters and digital advertisements for events and activities.

#### **EDUCATION**

MA in Interaction & UI/UX Design Academy of Art University (GPA 3.83/4.00)

San Francisco, CA 2021 - 2023

**BFA** in Illustration **Academy of Art University** 

San Francisco, CA 2016 - 2021